Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory02 Mss.B.B61.inventory02
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents B
  - Brody, Philip M. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 10; 2p
  - Brogger, A.W. (Box 11)
    - To Nansen, F., 1926 Apr. 12; 6p
  - Bromfield, Louis (Box 11)
    - see FB open letter, 1941 July 18
      - co-signer
    - To Boas, 1941 Sep. 9; 1p
  - Bromley, J.R. (Box 11)
    - see C. King, 1931 Sep. 26
      - co-signed: C. King & A. Taub
  - Brondel, Viggo (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 12; 2p
  - Brone (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 2p
  - Bronk, Detlev W. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 10; 1p
  - Bronson, R.M. (Box 11)
    - To W.C. Ryan, Jr., 1935 Sep. 18; 2p
      - enc. Collier, J., 1935 Sep. 24
  - Bronson, W.S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 9; 1p
  - Bronx Tuberculosis & Health Committee (Box 11)
    see Adams, Gladys A.
  - Brook, R.W. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1930 May 22; 2p
  - Brooklyn College. Faculty (Box 11)
    - Letters in N.Y. Times, 1941 Oct. 9
      - enc. H.D. Gideonse, 1941 Oct. 23
    - From H.D. Gideonse, 1941 Nov. 25
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts & Sciences (Box 11)
    - To FB from Sec'y, 1932 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Brooks,? (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct.
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct.
  - Brooks, A.C. (Box 11)
    - To J. Waterman, 1917 Apr. 12; 3p
  - Brooks, C.F. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Brooks, J. Chadwick (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 July 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 2p
      enc. Hudson's Bay Co. info.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 5; 2p
    - JCB -- to C.M. Barbeau, 1938 Dec. 2; 2p
  - Brooks, Jerome E. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 6; 1p
  - Brooks, Mary L. (Box 11)
    - Mrs. Boas -- to MLB, 1900 Oct. 12; 3p
    - MLB -- to Mrs. Boas, 1900?
    - MLB -- to Mrs. Boas, 1900 Oct. 10
    - MLB -- to Mrs. Boas, 1900?; 13p
  - Brooks, Van Wyck (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 22; 1p
      - co-signers: T. Arnold
      - George S. Kaufman
      - H.P. Fairchild
      - Marg. C. Banning
      - Ruth McKenney
      - Langston Hughes
      - Donald Ogden Stewart
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 2p
  - Broomall, C.M. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Broomall, H.L. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 14
  - Brouwer, L.E. (Box 11)
    - To Kerkhof, 1922 Dec. 10; 1p
  - Browder, Earl (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1941 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas
      see FB to F.D. Roosevelt
      - enc. with FB to Francis Biddle, 1941 Nov. 12
      - see FB, 1942 Dec. 21
      - Earl Browder Case, 12p
      - see FB open letter, 1942 Mar. 12
    - EB -- to Rockwell Kent, 1939 Feb. 20; 1p
      - enc with Frances Kent, 1939 Feb. 23
  - Brower Brothers (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
  - Brown,? (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 26; 1p
  - Brown, A.F. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 27
  - Brown, Arlo A. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4
  - Brown, C. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 8; 2p
  - Brown, D.M. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 3; 1p
  - Brown, E.E. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 10
    - From Boas, 1910 June 16
    - From Boas, 1910 July 2
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 16
  - Brown, E.N. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 9
  - Brown, H.O. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Brown, J. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p
  - Brown, J.C. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 9; 2p
  - Brown, Jack (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 1p
  - Brown, J.E. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 21; 1p
  - Brown, Mrs. John Crosby (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1901 Apr. 23; 2p
  - Brown, L.F. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 19; 1p
  - Brown, L.P. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1909 June 10
    - To Boas, 1909 June 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 June 7
  - Brown, M. -- from Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p (Box 11)
  - Brown, Percy S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 20; 1p
  - Brown, Ralph A. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 11; 1p
  - Brown University (Box 11)
    - see FB to Princeton Univ. sec'y, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
  - Brownson, Gladys (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 17; 2p
  - Bruce, E. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Bruce, L.E. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 6; 1p
  - Bruce, R.C., Gov. of B.C. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 4p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 18; 1p
    - RCB -- from W.E. Ditchburn, 1930 Dec. 13
      - enc. with A.M.D. Fairnbairn, 1930 Dec. 19
  - Bruce, R.E. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1906 May 7
  - Bruch, H. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 6; 2p
  - Bruch, S.S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Brückner, E., Prof. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1900 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 29; 4p
  - Brückner, H. -- to Boas, 1900 Oct. 14; 1p (Box 11)
  - Brückner, W. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 1p
  - Bruckner Society of America (Box 11)
    - See enc. Robt. G. Grey, 1931 July 17
  - Bruct, W.P. (Box 11)
    - open letter, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p
  - Bruder, V.W. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p
    - see FB to J.M. Tyler, 1919 Nov. 13
  - Brühl, Gustav (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1887 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1887 Sep. 25; 3p
    - To Boas, before 1887 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1887 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Sep. 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 21; 2p
  - Bruna, J.J. -- From Boas, 1924 Sep. 2 (Box 11)
  - Bruncken, Ernest (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 28; 1p
  - Bruno, H.A. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 29; 1p
  - Brunton, W.T. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 2; 5p
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 May 26
  - Brüser, E. (Box 11)
    - From Gramm, H., 1929 Jan. 30
      enc. with Gram
  - Bruster, W.T. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 8
  - Brutzkus, B. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p
  - Bruyn, Gertrude V. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 15; 1p
  - Bryan, Helen R. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 21; 2p
      - co-signer: C.B. Fauset, 1933 Jan. 6; 1p
      - enc. MRB to A.B. Spingara, 1933 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p
      - list enc., 1933 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr 27; 1p
      - list enc., Am. Rescue Ship Mission, 1941 Jan. 17; 2p
    - To Herskovits, M.J., 1933 Apr. 10
    - To Johnson, C.S., 1933 Dec. 5
    - To Keppel, F.P., 1933 Mar. 30
    - To Loram, C.T., 1933 Nov. 29
    - To List of Persons and Minutes, Inst. Race Relations, 1933 Apr. 8
    - To Spingarn, A.B., 1933 Jan. 6; 3p
  - Bryan, Keith W. (Box 11)
    - From George Hunt, 1931, Sep. 12; 1p
  - Bryan, Kirk (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
  - Bryan, Ruth W. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 21; 1p
    - see FB open letter, 1937 Feb. 4
    - To Aginsky, E., 1935 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Garfield, V.E., 1932 July 22; 1p
    - To Jacobs, M., 1932 July 20; 1p
    - To Tozzer, A.M., 1931 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Davis, W., 1931 Jan. 8
    - From Garfield, V.E., 1932 Aug. 19
    - From Heuser, F.W.J., 1940 Jan. 19
    - From Hunt, E.P., 1935 June 21
    - From Hunt, George, 1929 July 14
    - From Jacobs, M., 1932 July 13
    - From Jochelson, W., 1930 Sep. 6
    - From Jochelson, W., 1930 Sep. 28
    - From Jochelson, W., 1930 Oct. 16
    - From Kellogg, V., 1930 Dec. 18
      - (attached to FB), 1931 Jan. 13
    - From Kent, R.G., 1930 Sep. 12
    - From Lincoln, Helen, 1932 Feb. 5
    - From Livingston, B.E., 1931 Jan. 5
    - From Nelson, E.G., 1932 Aug. 6
    - From Oetteking, B., 1934 July 26
    - From Rau C., 1927 July 29
    - From Sherman, Mrs. S.P., 1936 Sep. 28
    - From Weitzner, Bella, 1942 Apr. 20
  - Bryan, Wm. L. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1894 May 13
  - Bryan, Wm. M. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 3p
  - Bryant, F.E. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 29
  - Bryant, Henry G. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 23; 1p
  - Bryce, James (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 24
  - Bryn Mawr College (Box 11)
    - From Boas to Librarian, 1921 Feb. 3; 1p
      See Taft, Helen M.
  - Btylon, E. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 21
  - Buchanan, Annabel M. (Mrs. John P.) (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1934 July 25; 2p
  - Buchanan, C.M. (Box 11)
    - To Hodge, F.W., 1913 Dec. 7; 2p
  - Buchanan, F. de S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 27; 3p
  - Buchdruckerei u. Verlaganstalt (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1924 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 June 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 10; 1p
  - Bucherei u. Bildungsflege (Box 11)
    - Excerpts, 1933 Dec. 28; 4p
  - Buchhandlung Gsellius (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Buchner, M. (Box 11)
    Native American Images note
    Pencil sketch
    - To Boas, 1895 May 24; 3p
  - Büchner & Lempke (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 1p
      (List enclosed)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 10; 1p
  - Buck, Prof. Carl D. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Buck, W.H. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 8; 2p
  - Bucky, G. (Box 11)
    - see Prokosch, E., 1933 Sep. 11
      - co-signers: Mankiewicz, F.
      - Klapper, P.
  - Buddenbrock, W. von (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 1; 2p
  - Budington, E.H. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
  - Buechel, Eugene (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 8; 2p
  - Buenz, Karl G. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1904 May 20
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 24; 1p
    - see Butler, N.M., 1908 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 19; 2p
    - CGB -- to Kepler, N.M., 1906 Mar. 16
  - Buerger, M.J. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1937 May 5; 1p
  - Buff & Buff (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Buford, F.J. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1890 July 8
  - Buford, T. Jay (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1890 May 9
  - Bühler, K. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 21; 2p
  - Buhlig, Paul (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
  - Buhn (?), P. von (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1929 July 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Bukwisti (?), M.W. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1916 July 5; 4p
  - Bulkley, E.W. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 7
  - Bull, N.L. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 3; 1p
  - Bullard, F.H. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 3; 1p
  - Bulloch, C.C. (Mrs. W.K.) (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1924 July 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 31; 6p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 19; 2p
  - Bullock-Webster, L. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Bullowa, Alfred L.M. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 23; 1p
  - Bumpus, H.C. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 May 5
    - From Boas, 1905 May 6; 4p
    - From Boas, 1905 May 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 May 18
    - From Boas, 1905 June 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 13 and Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1906 May 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 23 & Apr. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1908 June 3
    - From Boas, 1908 June 19
    - From Boas, 1908 June 23
    - FB -- to Bumpus?, 1909 Dec.
    - To Boas, 1902 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1905 May 5
    - To Boas, 1905 May 6
    - To Boas, 1905 May 10
    - To Boas, 1905 July 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
      - see F. Boas, 1906 May 25
    - To Boas, 1906 May 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 June 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 June 4
    - To Boas, 1909 May 4
    - To Boas, 1909 June 4
    - To Boas, 1909 June 21
    - HCB -- to E.J. Brill, 1904 Apr. 23
  - Bundesamt für Statistik Vienna, Austria (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 March 6; 1p
  - Bunker, F.F. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 28; 1p
    - FFB -- to Kerkhof, 1932 Dec. 29; 1p
  - Bunny (Box 12)
    see Bunzel, Ruth L.
  - Bünz, K. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 19; 2p
  - Bunzel, Ruth L. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1923 Nov. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Nov. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 July 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 10, 1927 Nov. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 5; 8p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 15; 5p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 28; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 4p
      - enc. Report, 1927 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov.; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 13; 2p
      - found end of year, 1929 Dec.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 3p
      - enc. Dec. 6 Report, 1930 Dec. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan 31; 2p
    - RIB -- from H.M. Adler, 1925 Feb. 27
    - RIB Report -- to Guggenheim Foundation, 1930 Dec. 6; 12 p
  - Burbey, Louis H. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 19; 1p
    - LHB -- to Augustin, J.J., 1939 Apr. 28; 1p
    - LHB -- to Augustin, J.J., 1939 May 16
  - Burbon, M. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 20
  - Burchard, Edward (Box 12)
    - Lists of donations, 1894 Mar. 23
  - Burchardi, K. (Box 12)
    - Frodm Boas, 1925 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 9; 2p
  - Burchenal, Elizabeth (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 9; 1p
  - Bureau of Jewish Social Research, Dir. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 27; 1p
  - Burgersdijk & Niermans (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Burgess, G.K. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
  - Burgess, John S. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
  - Burgess, John W. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1909 May 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1920 May 12; 2p
  - Burghardt, Geo. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 20
  - Burglon, N.P. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
  - Burgum, Edwin Berry (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 27; 1p
    - see FB Open letter, Spain, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas
      - Co-signer: A. Shukotoff
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec.; 1p
  - Burkitt, Edward (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1905 July 14
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
  - Burkitt, R. (Box 12)
    - To C.P. Bewditch, 1906 Feb. 16
  - Burks, Barbara S. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 23; 2p
      - enc., 1938 June 15; 1p
      - enc., 1939 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p
    - BBS -- to G.D. Stoddard, 1929 Apr. 27; 2p
    - From S. Van S. Theis, 1937 July 28
    - From S. Van S. Theis, 1938 July 28
    - From S. Van S. Theis, 1939 July 28
    - To D. Trachtenberg, 1941 Jan. 9; 1p
  - Burlin, N.C. (Box 12)
    see also Curtis, N.C.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Sep. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 24; 6p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 6; 2p
  - Burlin, Mrs. P. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 31; 2p
  - Burlingham, C.C. (Box 12)
    - From W.E. Dodd, 1939 Feb. 3
      - enc. with A.E. Kahn, 1939 Feb.
  - Burnet, A.C. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 2p
  - Burnett, I. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1884 Dec. 8
  - Burnett, Jeannie (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1884 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1885 Oct. 5
  - Burnham, A.A. (Box 12)
    - To Butler, N.M., 1906 Mar. 14
  - Burnham, M.T. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 28
  - Burnham, W.H. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Burns, Ralph A. (Box 12)
    - see FB Open letter, Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Burnside, C.H. (Box 12)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 13
  - Burney, William (Box 12)
    - To creditors of Columbia Estate Co., 1912 July 26
  - Burr, C.W. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 12
  - Burr, Emily T. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p
  - Burr, G.L. (George Lincoln) (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 17; 2p
  - Burroughs, Eric (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 10; 1p
  - Burroughs, Henrietta (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 25; 1p
  - Burroughs Brothers Co. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1905 May 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 May 8
  - Burrows, E.G. (Box 12)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p
  - Burrows, Elizabeth S. (Box 12)
    - To Paul W. Gordon, 1933 Sep. 2; 2p